Congratulations! The curse is gone!
축하합니다! 저주가 사라졌습니다!
Our neighbors also did the same thing.
우리 이웃도 그랬어요 같은 것.
- How are they now? - They became a couple...
- 지금은 어떤가요? - 커플이 되었어요...
and got married.
그리고 결혼했습니다.
They now have five children!
지금은 다섯 명의 아이들이 있어요!
- Huh? - What?
- 응? - 뭐?
What if you two also end up together?
당신도 둘이라면 어떨까요? 결국 함께하게 될까?
Jade, I have something to tell you.
제이드, 나한테 있어 당신에게 할 말이 있어요.
Miss Jade!
미스 제이드!
This is you and Mister Kiko.
이 사람은 당신이고 키코 씨.
You and your boyfriend look cute together.
당신과 당신의 남자친구 함께 보면 귀여워요.
No, he's not my boyfriend.
아니요, 그는 내 남자친구가 아닙니다.
He's my best friend.
그는 나의 가장 친한 친구입니다.
Prepare for our next meeting with Uncle Ronald.
다음을 준비하세요 로널드 삼촌과의 만남.
- We have another meeting? - Shh. Quiet.
- 또 회의가 있나요? - 쉿. 조용히.
Why are you shushing me?
왜 나를 조용히 시키시나요?
Because this is a personal meeting.
왜냐하면 이것은 개인 회의.
Sari, promise me you won't tell anyone else.
사리, 그러지 않겠다고 약속해요 다른 사람에게 말하세요.
Did you find out anything?
뭔가 알아낸 게 있나요?
I got Sandro Soliman's previous home address.
산드로 솔리만(Sandro Soliman)의 작품을 받았어요 이전 집 주소.
Okay, send it to me.
좋아요, 나에게 보내주세요.
- Sari. - Oh.
- 사리. - 오.
Martin is still in the restroom.
마틴은 아직도 화장실에서.
Ah...
아...
It's you I wanted to talk to.
내가 원한 건 바로 너야 이야기하다.
I know that Martin is expecting me to say yes now.
마틴이 기대하고 있다는 걸 알아요 지금 예라고 말하겠습니다.
[CHUCKLES]
[웃음]
Sari...
사리...
What do you like about Martin?
당신은 무엇을 좋아하나요? 마틴에 대해서?
Sorry?
죄송합니다?
[CHUCKLES]
[웃음]
I just want to know what you like about him
난 그냥 알고 싶어 그 사람의 어떤 점이 마음에 드나요
that made you become his girlfriend.
그게 너를 이렇게 만들었어 그의 여자친구.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
[어색하게 웃는다]
I-- W-- What?
나-- W-- 뭐?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[둘 다 웃음]
Don't be shy.
부끄러워하지 마세요.
Tell me.
말해 주세요.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[소프트 음악 재생]
He gave me an umbrella.
그는 나에게 우산을 주었다.
An umbrella?
우산?
[CHUCKLES]
[웃음]
That's it?
그게 다야?
When I first met him, it was raining.
그 사람을 처음 만났을 때, 비가 내리고 있었다.
- [THUNDER RUMBLING] - [RAIN POURING]
- [천둥소리] - [비가 쏟아진다]
We still didn't know each other that time.
우리는 아직 서로를 몰랐어요 그 때 다른.
He saw me getting drenched in rain,
그 사람은 내가 점점 받는 걸 봤어 비에 흠뻑 젖어
so he handed me an umbrella.
그래서 그 사람이 나한테 건네줬어 우산.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
It might not be a big deal to others.
그렇지 않을 수도 있습니다 다른 사람들에게는 큰 일입니다.
But for me, it showed that he's considerate,
하지만 나에게는 그것이 드러났다. 그 사람은 사려 깊다고
whether it be about business or personal stuff.
그것에 관한 것인지 사업이나 개인 물건.
Hmm.
흠.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[부드러운 음악이 계속됩니다]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[테마 음악 재생]
- Well? - What is it now?
- 잘? - 지금은 무엇입니까?
Come on, tell me. How did it go?
어서 말해 보세요. 어떻게 됐나요?
Did you tell her or will you keep it to yourself forever?
그녀에게 말했나요, 아니면 말할까요? 영원히 혼자만 간직하시겠습니까?
We didn't talk about anything, okay?
우리는 아무 얘기도 하지 않았어요. 알았지?
Oh come on, bro.
아, 어서요, 형.
What's with you?
당신은 무엇입니까?
You mean you went there for nothing?
거기 갔다고 하던데요 아무것도 아닌데?
I'll do it next time.
다음에 할게요.
Yeah, right. Let's see where that will take you.
응, 맞아. 어디 보자 그러면 당신이 걸릴 것입니다.
Hold on. Why are you making this about me?
기다리다. 왜 당신은 나에 대해 이런 짓을 한다고?
You also have something to tell me, right?
너도 뭔가 있어 나한테 말하려고 하는 거 맞지?
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
You're really good at changing topics, aren't you?
넌 정말 변화를 잘하는구나 주제죠, 그렇죠?
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
- Bro, brace yourself. - What?
- 형, 정신 차려요. - 무엇?
- I'm going to be a manager! - Ow!
- 나는 매니저가 될거야! - 아야!
- Wow! - Yes!
- 우와! - 예!
- That was fast. Where? - Yeah.
- 빨랐어요. 어디? - 응.
Trixie is opening up a new bar,
트릭시가 열리네요 새로운 바,
and she wants me to manage it.
그리고 그녀는 나를 원해 그것을 관리하기 위해.
Oh, that's good. And it's just nearby.
아, 그거 좋네요. 그리고 바로 근처에 있어요.
- Yes. I know, right? - We can still see each other.
- 예. 나도 알아, 그렇지? - 우리는 아직도 서로를 볼 수 있어요.
When are you starting?
언제 시작하나요?
Well, after she buys the place.
글쎄, 그녀가 구매한 후에 장소.
Oh, it's not sure yet?
아, 아직 확실하지 않은데요?
I'd say a fifty-fifty chance.
나는 기회가 반반이라고 말하고 싶습니다.
Oh, dear.
이런.
You should've made it clear.
당신이 만들었어야 했어요 분명해요.
I said "I'm going to be a manager."
나는 "나는 될 것이다. 매니저야."
"Going."
"가고 있다."
Not now, but in the future.
지금은 아니지만 미래에는 말이죠.
Yes, but when?
응, 그런데 언제?
When the bar is ready.
바가 준비되면.
- It's-- Yes, I'll manage it. - When it's ready.
- 그건-- 네, 제가 처리하겠습니다. - 준비가 되면.
Maybe you should manage yourself.
아마도 당신은해야 할 것입니다 자신을 관리하십시오.
Do you have a manager already? [CHUCKLES]
당신은 가지고 있습니까? 벌써 매니저야? [웃음]
You could be a celebrity. [CHUCKLES]
당신은 될 수 있습니다 유명인. [웃음]
- Sari. - Oh. Yes?
- 사리. - 오. 예?
Sandwich?
샌드위치?
I've got banana chips too.
바나나칩도 있어요.
- I'll have banana chips. - There's coffee too.
- 바나나칩 먹을게요. - 커피도 있어요.
Oh. I prefer iced coffee.
오. 나는 아이스 커피를 더 좋아한다.
Just kidding. [CHUCKLES]
농담이에요. [웃음]
Where did you and Martin go?
당신은 어디에서 왔습니까? 마틴은 가?
Oh, we had a meeting with Uncle Ronald.
아, 우리 회의가 있었어 로널드 삼촌과 함께.
- Oh. - Mmm.
- 오. - 음.
- Uncle? - Mm-hmm.
- 삼촌? - 음-흠.
He's Martin's uncle?
그 사람이 마틴의 삼촌인가요?
No, he's the father of Sir Martin's friend.
아니요, 그 사람은 아버지예요 마틴 경의 친구.
Hmm. A personal meeting.
흠. 개인 회의.
Nope.
아니요.
Sir Martin is looking for investors.
마틴 선생님이 보고 계십니다 투자자를 위해.
Investors for what?
무엇을 위한 투자자인가?
[LUNA] We just had a team building and you do this?!
[루나] 우리에겐 팀이 있었어 건물을 짓고 이런 짓을 하는 거야?!
[MARTIN] What are you talking about?!
[마틴] 당신은 무엇입니까 얘기하는거야?!
[LUNA] Drop the act, Martin! You're busted.
[루나] 그만둬 마틴! 당신은 체포되었습니다.
You did that so you could get the upper hand.
넌 그럴 수 있도록 그렇게 했어 우위를 확보하십시오.
This just shows you have no idea how to run a business.
이것은 단지 당신에게 아무것도 없다는 것을 보여줍니다 사업을 운영하는 방법에 대한 아이디어.
Having business partners will help us get money.
비즈니스 파트너 보유 우리가 돈을 버는 데 도움이 될 거예요.
And you're manipulating it to your favor!
그리고 당신은 조작하고 있어요 당신의 호의에 그것을!
Martin, Luna, what's going on?
마틴, 루나, 무슨 일이야?
Why are you two fighting again?
왜 둘이? 또 싸워?
Your brother is getting investors without our knowledge.
네 동생이 점점 우리가 모르는 투자자들.
I wouldn't have known if Sari hadn't slipped up.
사리였으면 몰랐을 텐데 미끄러지지는 않았습니다.
What? Is that true, Martin?
무엇? 그게 사실인가요, 마틴?
Yes, I was talking to a possible investor.
응, 얘기 중이었어 가능한 투자자에게.
Why didn't you tell me and Leon about it?
왜 나한테 말하지 않았어? 그리고 레온은 그것에 대해?
Because it's not a done deal.
아직 완료된 거래가 아니기 때문입니다.
He still hasn't decided yet. Ask Sari.
그는 아직 결정하지 않았습니다. 사리에게 물어보세요.
Do you honestly think I'll still believe you?
솔직하게 생각하시나요? 그래도 당신을 믿을까요?
All you do is attack me.
당신이 하는 모든 일 나를 공격하고 있습니다.
Why don't you try to understand what I'm doing?
왜 노력하지 않니? 내가 뭘 하는지 알아?
I'm just protecting our family's interest!
나는 단지 보호하고 있을 뿐이다 우리 가족의 관심사!
And I'm protecting the hotel!
그리고 나는 보호하고 있어요 호텔!
This hotel is my family!
이 호텔은 내 가족이에요!
Our family doesn't have money,
우리 가족은 그렇지 않아요 돈이 있어
and you, Almazans, aren't doing anything
그리고 당신, Almazans는 그렇지 않습니다 뭐든지
to help get more money.
얻을 수 있도록 돕기 위해 더 많은 돈.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[불안한 음악 재생]
Don't you get it, Luna?
모르겠어, 루나?
We have to pay the bank loan urgently.
우리는 비용을 지불해야 급하게 은행 대출을 받았습니다.
As general manager, shouldn't that be your concern
총책임자로서 이러면 안 된다. 그게 네 걱정이겠지
instead of your family's interests?!
너의 대신에 가족의 관심사?!
I promised Dad I'd do everything for our family,
아빠한테 그러겠다고 약속했어요 우리 가족을 위한 모든 것
and that includes this hotel.
여기에는 이 호텔도 포함됩니다.
I won't let you and your family get full control of this hotel!
너와 네 가족을 가만두지 않을 거야 이 호텔을 완전히 장악하세요!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[불안한 음악이 계속됨]
- Tea? - [KEYBOARD CLICKING]
- 차? - [키보드 클릭]
Or sympathy?
아니면 동정심?
What?
무엇?
Are you sure about the bar business?
확실합니까? 바 사업?
Yes, Martin.
응, 마틴.
I just have a small problem, but I can handle it.
그냥 작은 문제가 생겼어요 하지만 난 감당할 수 있어.
Do you need my help?
내 도움이 필요합니까?
[TRIXIE CLICKS TONGUE] No, I got it.
[트릭시가 혀를 찰칵] 아니요, 알겠습니다.
You already have enough on your plate.
당신은 이미 당신의 접시에 충분합니다.
Actually, I should be the one helping you.
사실 난 그래야만 해 당신을 돕는 사람.
That's why I'm here,
그래서 내가 여기 있는 거야,
to help you when you need a breather.
당신을 돕기 위해 숨이 필요할 때.
I mean, you and Luna were shouting at each other earlier.
내 말은, 당신과 루나는 아까부터 서로 소리쳤어요.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[깊이 숨을 들이쉰다]
Luna's only like that, because she's threatened by me.
루나는 딱 그래요. 그 사람이 나한테 협박을 당했으니까.
She knows I should be the GM,
그녀는 내가 GM이 되어야 한다는 걸 알고 있어
and I can do so much of a better job than her.
그리고 난 정말 많은 일을 할 수 있어 그 사람보다 더 나은 직업을 갖고 있지.
True.
진실.
But you guys are starting to get along, right?
그런데 너희들은 이제 시작이야 어울리려고 그러는 거 맞지?
And your move to talk to Uncle Ronald?
그리고 당신의 이사 로널드 삼촌이랑 얘기해볼까?
That was a bit sneaky.
좀 은밀했어요.
[SCOFFS] Fine.
[비웃음] 좋아요.
It started that way.
그렇게 시작되었습니다.
I wanted to gain a partner,
파트너를 얻고 싶었어요
so my siblings and I could benefit from them.
그래서 나와 내 형제들은 그들로부터 이익을 얻을 수 있습니다.
[MARTIN] But right now, my priority
[마틴] 하지만 지금은 내 우선순위
is paying off our debt to the bank,
우리 빚을 갚고 있어 은행으로
so we don't lose Hotel 88.
그래서 우리는 호텔 88을 잃지 않습니다.
Okay.
좋아요.
So, what's your plan now?
그럼 이제 당신의 계획은 무엇입니까?
Will you stop talking to Uncle Ronald?
말 좀 그만 할래? 로널드 삼촌에게?
Huh? Why?
뭐? 왜?
Why would I do that?
내가 왜 그럴까요?
Martin.
남자 이름.
You and Luna are clashing because of that.
당신과 루나가 충돌하고 있어요 그것 때문에.
So, if Luna and I are okay,
그럼 루나와 내가 괜찮다면
will that pay off our bank debt?
그게 우리 은행 빚을 갚을 수 있을까?
No.
아니요.
But...
하지만...
...come on, Martin.
...어서, 마틴.
Business is business, Trixie.
사업은 사업이다, 트릭시.
You should know that by now.
지금쯤이면 그 사실을 알아야 합니다.
Don't worry about me.
나에 대해 걱정하지 마세요.
I can stand by by decisions.
나는 결정을 내릴 수 있습니다.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[침울한 음악 재생]
I know.
알아요.
I believe in you.
나는 당신을 믿습니다.
But, Martin, you need to tell Gio.
하지만 마틴, 지오한테 말해야 해.
[TRIXIE] All your siblings need to know about this.
[트릭시] 네 형제자매 모두 이것에 대해 알아야합니다.
Leave it to me, Trixie.
나에게 맡겨주세요, 트릭시.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[음악이 계속됨]
Martin, are you okay?
마틴, 괜찮아?
Be honest. There's something off about you.
솔직해지세요. 뭔가가 있어요 당신에 대해.
Why wouldn't be I okay?
나는 왜 괜찮지 않을까?
Martin, if this is about you
마틴, 이게 당신에 관한 것이라면
trying to prove something to Dad...
증명하려고 노력 중 아빠에게 뭔가를...
Trixie.
트릭시.
I'm fine.
잘 지내요.
Okay.
좋아요.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[음악이 계속됨]
So, Ma, you'll be all alone in that house.
그럼 엄마, 그럴 거예요 그 집에 혼자 있어요.
Are you okay with that?
괜찮으세요?
[GEORGIA] What if I say I don't agree with this?
[GEORGIA] 내가 말하면 어쩌지? 나는 이것에 동의하지 않습니까?
Ma, you know, out of all the moms,
엄마, 아시죠? 모든 엄마들 중에서,
you're not clingy at all.
당신은 전혀 집착하지 않습니다.
[LAUGHS]
[웃음]
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
I'm the most understanding mom ever.
내가 가장 엄마를 이해해 주세요.
I haven't seen you two for so long,
나는 너희 둘을 본 적이 없다 오랫동안
and I only receive messages from you,
그리고 나는 단지 받기만 합니다 당신이 보낸 메시지,
have I ever complained?
내가 불평한 적이 있나요?
No, right?
아니, 그렇죠?
That's why I'm the most understanding
그래서 내가 가장 이해하기
Mother of the Year.
올해의 어머니.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
Yes, Ma.
응, 엄마.
You're the most understanding mom ever.
당신은 가장 엄마를 이해해.
And besides, you two are adults already.
게다가 너희 둘은 벌써 어른이 되었네요.
As long as you don't cheat, you don't steal,
속이지 않는 한, 넌 훔치지 않아,
you don't do drugs, and you don't kill people,
당신은 마약을 하지 않으며, 넌 사람을 죽이지 않아,
I'm fine.
난 괜찮아.
- I'm happy with that. - But...
- 만족스럽습니다. - 하지만...
Ma, I can't help but notice and mention it.
엄마, 눈치채지 않을 수가 없어요 그리고 그것을 언급하십시오.
It's like...
그것은 마치...
...your hair's so perfect, Ma.
...머리가 정말 완벽해요, 엄마.
I noticed it when the call started.
나는 그것을 깨달았다. 통화가 시작되었습니다.
- [KIKO GIGGLES]
- [키코 낄낄거림]
- What's happening? - Uh...
- 무슨 일이에요? - 어...
[CHESCA] I think Mommy has a new boyfriend.
[체스카] 내 생각엔 엄마 새 남자친구가 생겼어요.
You've got a new boyfriend, don't you, Ma?
당신은 새로운 것을 가지고 남자친구, 그렇지 않나요, 엄마?
That's the reason why you don't want us there.
그렇기 때문에 당신은 우리가 거기 있는 걸 원하지 않아요.
Uh...
어...
Let us see your nails, Ma. Come on.
손톱 좀 볼까요, 엄마. 어서 해봐요.
Let us see!
보자!
Why?
왜?
What's wrong with you two?
너희 둘에게 무슨 문제가 있는 걸까?
My goodness.
이럴 수가.
Fine. Here.
괜찮은. 여기.
- We knew it! [GIGGLES] - Yeah!
- 우리는 그것을 알고 있었습니다! [GIGGLES] - 응!
Ma, I'm not good at giving manicures.
엄마, 나 잘 못해요 매니큐어를 줘요.
But I know what that color means.
하지만 나도 알아 그 색깔은 의미합니다.
Ma, you usually get that color when you like a new guy.
엄마, 보통 그런 색깔이시죠? 새로운 남자가 마음에 들 때.
Hold on, kids. Calm down.
잠깐만요, 아이들. 진정하다.
He's only courting me.
그는 단지 나에게 구애하고 있습니다.
And if he fools me, he'll go straight to jail, because--
그리고 그가 나를 속이면 가버릴 거예요 바로 감옥에 갈 테니까--
Ma, is it the Captain?
엄마, 선장님이세요?
Your new boyfriend is the Captain, Ma?
당신의 새로운 남자 친구 캡틴이에요, 엄마?
Shush! Watch your mouth.
쉿! 입 조심하세요.
The Captain's married!
선장이 결혼했습니다!
It's Elmer, the guy who works for him.
엘머예요. 그 사람 밑에서 일하는 사람.
He's single.
그는 싱글입니다.
[KIKO] Ma, just be careful.
[KIKO] 엄마, 조심하세요.
And if that man ever hurts you,
그리고 그 사람이 당신에게 상처를 준 적이 있다면,
I'll bring my two brothers, and get back at him.
나는 내 두 형제를 데리고 올 것이다. 그리고 그에게 다시 돌아오세요.
Mhm-hmm.
음-흠.
Of course.
물론이죠.
Thank you, my very protective eldest son.
감사합니다. 나의 매우 보호적인 큰 아들.
No, but seriously.
아니, 하지만 심각하게요.
Let's be serious for a while.
잠시 진지하게 생각해보자.
Don't worry about me, kids.
내 걱정은 하지 마세요, 얘들아.
I'm doing fine here.
나는 여기서 잘 지내고 있어요.
Leave our vegetable store to me.
야채가게는 나에게 맡겨주세요.
I'm happy to see you two stick together.
만나서 반가워요 너희 둘은 꼭 붙어있어.
[GEORGIA] But promise me one thing.
[조지아] 하지만 한 가지만 약속해 주세요.
No matter what happens...
무슨 ​​일이 있어도...
No matter what happens,
무슨 일이 일어나든
always remember to take care of yourselves,
항상 기억해 몸 조심하세요
and each other, okay?
그리고 서로, 알았지?
[KIKO] Of course, Ma.
[키코] 물론이죠, 엄마.
I'll take care of this one.
이건 내가 처리할게.
I'll take care of Kiko, Ma,
키코는 내가 돌볼게, 엄마
especially when he's causing trouble.
특히 이럴 때 그 사람이 문제를 일으키고 있어.
[GEORGIA] I miss you, kids.
[조지아] 보고 싶어, 얘들아.
- I miss you, Ma.
- 보고 싶어요, 엄마.
- Love you. - I love you.
- 사랑해요.
Sir, please. Sir.
선생님, 제발요. 선생님.
Sir.
선생님.
- Hello. Good evening. - Good evening.
- 안녕하세요. 좋은 저녁이에요. - 좋은 저녁이에요.
Sir, please? [CRIES]
선생님, 제발요? [울음]
- Sir. - Wait.
- 선생님. - 기다리다.
Don't close that room yet.
아직 그 방을 닫지 마세요.
Okay, sir.
알겠습니다.
Come with me.
나와 함께 가자.
Sir.
선생님.
Tell me what it is!
그것이 무엇인지 말해 보세요!
Because I don't want our guests outside to hear
나는 우리를 원하지 않기 때문에 밖에 손님들이 듣기 위해
just how incompetent the people who work here are!
얼마나 무능한지 여기서 일하는 사람들은 바로!
Sir, I didn't mean to tell Miss Luna about Sir Ronald.
선생님, 그럴 생각은 아니었어요 미스 루나에게 로널드 경에 대해 말해주세요.
I told you that was a secret, right?!
내가 말했잖아 비밀이었죠, 그렇죠?!
I forgot, sir. I'm so sorry.
잊어버렸어요, 선생님. 정말 죄송해요.
[MARTIN SCOFFS]
[마틴 비웃음]
Is that all you want to say?
당신이 말하고 싶은 건 그게 전부인가요?
Yes.
예.
I think we need some time apart.
내 생각엔 우리에게 필요한 것 같아 시간이 좀 떨어져요.
What, sir? "Time apart?"
뭐라고요? "시간이 떨어져 있나요?"
[MARTIN] Yes. Leave.
[마틴] 네. 떠나다.
- Leave! - [GASPS]
- 떠나다! - [가스프]
- [SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING] - [FOOTSTEPS MOVING AWAY]
- [침울한 음악 재생] - [멀어지는 발자국]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[불안한 음악 재생]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[음악이 계속됨]
#22 RUCIO ST. COSTA VIDA
#22 루시오 스트리트 코스타 비다
[BUZZER RINGS]
[버저 울림]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[음악이 계속됨]
[GATE CLINKS]
[게이트 땡땡이]
[GATE CREAKING]
[게이트 삐걱거리는 소리]
[GATE CONTINUES CREAKING DISTANTLY]
[게이트는 계속된다 멀리 삐걱거리는 소리]
[MUSIC CONTINUES, SWELLS]
[음악이 계속되고 부풀어 오른다]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[우울한 음악 재생]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[다가오는 발자국]
[JUSTIN WHISPERS] Hey, Juan! Juan!
[저스틴 속삭임] 안녕, 후안! 후안!
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
My brother doesn't know I'm here. I just followed him.
내 동생은 몰라 나는 여기 있다. 나는 단지 그를 따랐다.
Your brother is here?
네 동생이 여기 있어?
What are you? The lookout?
당신은 무엇입니까? 전망대?
You're accomplices.
당신들은 공범자입니다.
What brings you to my dad's house?
무엇이 당신을 데려오나요? 아빠 집으로?
I don't even know!
나도 모르겠어요!
I didn't know this was your house!
나는 이것을 몰랐다 네 집이었어!
You won't get anything out of my brother if you see him.
당신은 아무것도 얻을 수 없습니다 내 동생을 본다면.
I know my brother, he's stubborn.
나는 내 동생을 알고, 그는 고집이 세다.
You won't get anything out of him
당신은 얻지 못할 것이다 그 사람에게서 나온 건 뭐든지
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[긴장된 음악 재생]
- Leon. - Shh!
- 레온. - 쉿!
[GATE CREAKS]
[게이트 삐걱거림]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[긴장된 음악이 계속됨]
Don't follow my brother.
내 동생을 따르지 마세요.
Want to find out where your dad is
알고 싶다 네 아버지는 어디 계시니
and what my brother knows?
그리고 내 동생이 뭘 알아?
l'll help you.
내가 도와줄게.
I'm an Almazan.
저는 알마잔입니다.
I have a lot of connections!
인맥이 많아요!
You won't need Leon anymore.
더 이상 레온이 필요하지 않습니다.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[긴장된 음악이 계속됨]
- [MUSIC BOX PLAYING] - [MARTIN] All you do is attack!
- [뮤직박스 재생 중] - [마틴] 당신이 하는 일은 공격뿐입니다!
Why don't you try to understand what I'm doing?!
이해하려고 노력하지 그래? 내가 뭘 하고 있는 거지?!
[LUNA] Because I'm protecting our family's interest!
[루나] 내가 지키고 있으니까 우리 가족의 관심사!
[MARTIN] And I'm protecting the hotel's interests!
[마틴] 그리고 난 보호하고 있어 호텔의 이익!
This hotel is my family. And you Almazans...
이 호텔은 나의 가족입니다. 그리고 당신 Almazans...
all you ever do is attack people!
당신이 하는 모든 일 공격하는 사람들입니다!
You never do anything to help us around!
넌 아무것도 안 해 우리를 도와주려고요!
[LUNA] I'm not going to let you down, Dad.
[LUNA] 안 가요 실망시키려고요, 아빠.
I won't let the past get in my way.
나는 허락하지 않을 것이다 방해하지 마세요.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[우울한 음악 재생]
[EXHALES]
[숨을 내쉬다]
Luna.
루나.
What are we doing here in Edward's place?
우리 여기서 뭐하는거야? 에드워드 대신에?
When you're done, could you serve it to them?
끝나면, 그들에게 그것을 제공할 수 있나요?
Luna?
루나?
- Hey, Dad. - [ANDY] Hey, bud.
- 안녕, 아빠. - [앤디] 안녕, 친구.
- Hey, Luna. - Uncle Andy.
- 안녕, 루나. - 앤디 삼촌.
[SMOOCHES]
[스무치]
- Uncle, hello. - Jade.
- 삼촌, 안녕하세요. - 제이드.
- Nice seeing you again. - Nice to see you again.
- 다시 만나서 반가워요.
Let's do it, Uncle.
해보자, 삼촌.
Really? You know, that's wonderful news.
정말? 아시다시피, 정말 좋은 소식이네요.
I'm more than willing to help you with the hotel.
나는 기꺼이 그 이상이다 호텔 이용을 도와드리기 위해.
Ah...
아...
Sorry?
죄송합니다?
H-help?
H-도움?
Ah... Luna, what does Uncle mean?
아... 루나, 삼촌은 무슨 뜻인가요?
[EDWARD] Didn't Luna say that...
[EDWARD] 루나가 그렇게 말하지 않았나요...
we'll invest in Hotel 88?
호텔 88에 투자할까요?
Partner?
파트너?
[JADE] Luna, you were looking for a partner?
[제이드] 루나 너였어 파트너를 찾고 있나요?
You knew about this?
당신은 이것에 대해 알고 있었나요?
- Jade... - Are you doing this
- 제이드... - 지금 이러고 있는 거야
because of what you fought about with Martin?
당신이 무엇 때문에 마틴이랑 싸웠어?
No, Jade.
아니, 제이드.
We've been talking about this for some time now.
우리는 이것에 대해 이야기 해왔다 지금은 한동안.
Um...
음...
Luna, I think it's best to talk to your siblings first.
루나, 얘기하는 게 좋을 것 같아 먼저 형제자매에게.
[CHUCKLES] It's okay, Uncle Andy.
[웃음] 괜찮아요 앤디 삼촌.
If I explain this to them,
내가 그들에게 이것을 설명하면
I'm sure we'll all have the same decision.
나는 우리 모두가 가질 것이라고 확신합니다 같은 결정.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[불안한 음악 재생]
[ANDY] Okay, then. As long as, uh...
[앤디] 그럼요. 그렇다면...
we're on the same page.
우리는 같은 페이지에 있습니다.
Just let me know when we will sign
언제인지 알려주세요. 서명하겠습니다
so we can inform our lawyers.
그래서 우리는 알릴 수 있습니다 우리 변호사들.
And, uh, Jade, I understand your concerns.
그리고, 어, 제이드, 나는 당신의 우려를 이해합니다.
You have nothing to worry about.
당신은 아무것도 없습니다 걱정하다.
Edward will be your partner,
에드워드가 당신의 파트너가 될 것입니다.
as he will be handling everything on our side.
그가 처리할 대로 우리 편의 모든 것.
Okay?
좋아요?
Thank you, Tito. I have also spoken to our lawyers.
고마워요, 티토. 나 또한 우리 변호사들과 얘기했어요.
They will just call you.
그들은 당신에게 전화할 것입니다.
[ANDY] Alright, good. Exciting times ahead.
[앤디] 알았어, 좋아. 앞으로는 흥미로운 시간이 될 것입니다.
Our families will finally become business partners.
우리 가족은 드디어 비즈니스 파트너가 됩니다.
[ANDY] Alright? I'll see you later.
[앤디] 알았어? 나중에 뵙겠습니다.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[불안한 음악이 계속됨]
You got so mad at Martin for talking to an investor.
마틴한테 너무 화났잖아 투자자와 이야기를 나누기 위해.
But you were talking to one too.
하지만 당신도 한 사람과 이야기하고 있었어요.
Luna, you knew we would fight about this.
루나, 우리 알고 있었잖아 이것에 대해 싸울 것입니다.
[LUNA] Jade, they did it first.
[루나] 제이드가 먼저 했어요.
I'm just fighting back.
나는 단지 반격하고 있습니다.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Edward.
에드워드.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[불안한 음악이 계속됨]
So this is your father's house.
그러니까 여기가 네 아버지 집이구나.
Are you doing this to hide the truth from me?
당신은 이것을하고 있습니까? 나에게 진실을 숨기려고?
What truth?
무슨 진실?
That your brother has something to do with Papa's disappearance.
네 동생이 뭔가를 가지고 있다고 아빠의 실종과 관련이 있습니다.
Is that what you think of us?
당신은 우리에 대해 그렇게 생각하나요?
Maybe it's Leon,
아마 레온일지도 몰라,
or you, or your entire family.
아니면 당신, 아니면 온 가족.
I just know you were involved in Papa's disappearance.
난 당신이 관여했다는 걸 알아요 아빠의 실종.
You have no proof that my family did anything.
당신은 그런 증거가 없습니다 우리 가족은 뭐든지 했어요.
But I know your father did something.
하지만 난 네 아버지를 알아 뭔가를 했어요.
Someone had him investigated.
누군가 그를 조사하게 했어요.
It says here that he was Uncle Mike's former contractor.
여기에 그가 있었다고 적혀 있어요 마이크 삼촌의 전 계약자.
He was the one who set fire to Hotel 88.
그 사람이 바로 그 사람이었어 호텔 88에 불을 지른 사람.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[불안한 음악 재생]
"...intentional in nature and consistent with arson."
"...본질상 의도적임 방화와 일치합니다."
"...consistent with intentional fire-setting behavior."
"...의도와 일치 방화 행위."
Arson!
방화!
It wasn't an accident.
그것은 사고가 아니었습니다.
That's not true.
그것은 사실이 아닙니다.
Why should I believe you?
내가 왜 당신을 믿어야합니까?
You and your brother are messing with me!
당신과 당신의 형제 나한테 장난을 치고 있어!
I swear, Leon doesn't know I'm doing this!
맹세코, 레온은 모른다 나는 이것을하고있다!
We are both looking for answers!
우리 둘 다 답을 찾고 있습니다!
You want to know what my brother had to do with your father?
내 동생이 뭔지 알고 싶어? 네 아버지랑 관련이 있었어?
That's the same question they refuse to answer!
같은 질문이군요 그들은 대답을 거부합니다!
But, fine!
하지만 괜찮아요!
Hit me!
나를 때려라!
But just to remind you,
하지만 다시 한번 말씀드리자면,
you've been following Leon for days
당신은 팔로우하고 있었습니다 며칠 동안 레온
and you've come up empty handed.
그리고 당신이 나타났어요 빈손으로.
But now, you've learned something from me.
하지만 이제 당신은 배웠습니다. 나한테서 뭔가가 왔어.
So tell me,
그럼 말해봐,
was it me or my brother?
나였어 아니면 내 동생이었어?
You're the only Almazan who can help me right now.
당신은 유일한 알마잔이에요 지금 당장 나를 도와줄 수 있는 사람.
But don't push my limits.
하지만 내 한계를 뛰어넘지는 마세요.
If I find out
내가 알아낸다면
you really are responsible for Papa's disappearance,
당신은 정말로 책임이 있습니다 아빠의 실종에 대해
you will all pay!
너희는 모두 지불할 것이다!
And that includes all of your siblings.
그리고 여기에는 다음이 포함됩니다 네 형제자매 모두.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[긴장된 음악 재생]
[LINE RINGING]
[라인 벨 울림]
Jade, where's Justin?
제이드, 저스틴은 어디 있어?
I don't know. He's not answering my calls.
모르겠습니다. 그는 내 전화에 응답하지 않습니다.
He is unbelievable.
그는 믿을 수 없습니다.
Luna.
루나.
We shouldn't make decisions when we're angry or emotional.
우리는 결정을 내려서는 안 된다 화가 났거나 감정적일 때.
Leon, Uncle Andy and I already made a deal before.
레온, 앤디 삼촌과 나 이미 전에 거래를 했어.
Then you're no different than Martin!
그럼 너도 다르지 않아 마틴보다!
I told Luna the same thing, Leon.
루나에게도 같은 말을 했어요. 레온.
- I don't care. - [LEON SCOFFS]
- 상관없어요. - [레온 비웃음]
If we are going to hire a new investor
우리가 갈 경우 새로운 투자자를 고용하려고
or partner for Hotel 88,
또는 Hotel 88의 파트너,
it should come from us.
그것은 우리에게서 나와야 합니다.
It should be Uncle Andy.
앤디 삼촌이겠죠.
Luna...
루나...
[LUNA] Uncle Andy is the right choice.
[루나] 앤디 삼촌 올바른 선택입니다.
Martin hasn't sealed the deal with his investor yet, right?
마틴은 거래를 성사시키지 않았습니다 그 사람 투자자랑은 아직 안 됐지?
But we need to talk to them first.
하지만 우리는 먼저 그들에게 말을 걸어보세요.
Martin said he's protecting the interest of the hotel.
마틴은 자신이 보호하고 있다고 말했어요 호텔의 관심.
If that is the case,
그렇다면
then he shouldn't turn down the investment of the Arellanos.
그럼 그 사람 거절하면 안 돼 Arellanos의 투자.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[긴장된 음악 재생]
Welcome to Hotel 88, sir!
Hotel 88에 오신 것을 환영합니다!
The hotel that has witnessed the secret stares of love.
목격한 호텔 은밀한 사랑의 눈빛.
Why do you feel insecure?
왜 불안감을 느끼시나요?
She's up here, I'm way down here.
그녀가 여기 있어요. 난 여기 훨씬 아래에 있어.
I can feel sparks between you and Sir Kiko, Miss Jade.
사이에 불꽃이 느껴집니다 당신과 키코 경과 제이드 씨.
I can feel it in my fingers,
손가락으로 느껴지는데요,
and in my hair...
그리고 내 머리에도...
in your heart!
당신의 마음속에!
[SQUEALING]
[비명소리]
Finish what you started.
시작한 일을 마무리하세요.
Don't get his hopes up.
그 사람에게 기대를 걸지 마세요.
But you're flirting with a guest!
근데 당신은 유혹을 하고 있어요 손님과 함께!
I don't care if you do this outside,
상관없어요 넌 밖에서 이런 짓을 해,
but don't you ever do it here in the hotel!
하지만 넌 절대 그러지 마 여기 호텔이에요!
So, you're going to run away with me?
그래서 당신은 달릴 거예요 나랑 같이 갈래?
So you can leave behind the negativity
남길 수 있도록 부정적인 면
that is making you sad.
그게 당신을 슬프게 만드네요.
I don't know if I still want him to be our hotel partner.
아직도 원하는지 모르겠어요 그를 우리 호텔 파트너로 삼고 싶습니다.
I have a bad feeling.
기분이 좋지 않습니다.
We need him. We're making him our partner.
우리에겐 그가 필요해요. 우리는 그를 파트너로 삼고 있습니다.
- A map of Hotel 88? - What's that?
- 호텔 88 지도요? - 그게 뭐죠?
I'm one step closer.
한 걸음 더 가까워졌습니다.
I'll access the places I've never been to at Hotel 88.
해당 장소에 액세스하겠습니다. 호텔 88에는 가본 적이 없어요.
If I didn't succeed at first,
성공하지 못했다면 처음에는
now I will.
이제 그럴게요.